catch guys maybe develop maybe a little
further along or in the development for
this net to jump to the next level.
>> Yeah. You know, I would say the
interesting thing with both of them is
they didn't start their careers at
Alabama, right? So Parker starts off at
Washington, transfers to Alabama. Justin
started off in Jo, transferred to
Alabama. Um both those guys had like a
developmental curve. Uh and with Parker
in particular, you know, I think it's
he's playing against the best of the
best in the SEC. So, he is matching up
against guys with size who he's going to
have to face in the NFL and and that is
something that maybe if you have a small
school guy who lacks size, you're making
more of a projection on how that'll play
out.
>> Justin, what did you guys like about him
and what do you kind of envision him
adding to that linebacker room and it
looks like maybe special teams too.
>> Yeah, really nice scheme fit first and
foremost. I mean, we have played with um
you know Devin Bush, we signed Quincy
Williams. Both of those guys are around
the same size, six foot, really fast,
really athletic. So, just a real clean
and vision for how he fits into the
scheme. Um, and then when you have guys
who can run 44, um, and like to hit,
that translates pretty well on special
teams. So, I think, you know, Justin
both on defense and on special teams
will have a nice role.
>> With the four fifth round picks, was
there any effort to move up in the
round?
>> That's something we discussed. Yeah. and
discuss moving up. Obviously, we moved
back, you know, with one of the picks
and we moved out entirely with one of
the picks. So,
>> state center went a few notches ahead of
your center
>> there. There was there was a run on the
centers, but to be honest, Parker was
the guy we had targeted all along.
>> Did he get bigger or is this his 289
size?
>> He played in the high 280s, you know,
low 290s. I think he is more than
capable at functioning. He's at in terms
of his weight.
>> Obviously, you guys have devoted a bunch
of resources the offensive line in the
last month and a half. Coming into the
draft, how important or how much of a
focus was it to add somebody in that
center?
>> I wouldn't say there's a focus at one
particular spot. I think the focus was
adding good players along the offensive
line. Um, I think it's been noted we've
added guys with positional versatility.
That's important. We know that you're
going into the year you're going to have
your starting five, but the reality is
you're going to play with more than
five. I think last year the top if you
played more than 50% of your snaps with
your top five linemen, you would have
been in the top 10 in the league. So,
you're going to have to cover, you know,
a th00and 2,000 snaps somewhere on the
line with other guys usually the way
injuries go. So, you know, I think we
just were focused on getting good
players who could play on the line and
then, you know, figuring out the
configuration from there.
>> And do you think um are some positions
uh easier for guys drafted later to
succeed than others, such as getting
Parker here in this role?
I think there are certain positions
within certain schemes that you might
anticipate a quicker transition, you
know, going from college to pro, but I
do think it's it's across schemes more
than maybe necessarily across positions.
>> Trade out of the third round then back
in. Is that kind of what he's doing with
this trade
down to the six round
back up or I don't see the logic in
that? No, I think we just got, you know,
a really good offer to to draw it back
in five and still pick up an extra pick,
you know, nearby. So 170 and 182. Um,
with, you know, feel pretty confident
that the same kind of set of players
that we would consider there will be
available, you know, a few few slots
later.
>> Thanks,